Contact

03063213951 (Work) zuhaibahmed3213951@gmail.co m

www.linkedin.com/in/zuhaibah (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Responsiveness
Web Maintenance
Site Build

Languages

English (Professional Working)
French (Limited Working)
Spanish (Limited Working)
German (Limited Working)
Arabic (Limited Working)

Certifications

Certified Web Professional - Site Designer (CWP)

Zuhaib Ahmed

WordPress Specialist | Generated over 100k\$ Sales On Clients Sites | Student of GenAl, Web3 and Metaverse

Sukkur, Sindh, Pakistan

Summary

The words I use to describe myself are: creative web designer & developer with 4 years of experience in the design and customization of WordPress websites. I aim to provide highly professional, responsive, and high-quality services using my academic and professional knowledge of web design.

Experience

Fiverr

6 years

WordPress Developer | Web Developer | Web Designer April 2021 - Present (3 years 6 months)

Pakistan

Do you wanna see creativity in your website that reflects a creative and fascinating web design? I'm here to do this job for YOU. I'm a professionally trained Website Designer and Developer with three years of Amazing experience at design and customization of WordPress Sites. My service is to provide you utmost Professional, Responsive and High-quality services and features. Its guaranteed because of my academic and professional knowledge at Website development

WordPress website designer July 2021 - Present (3 years 3 months) Remotely

- Website designing
- Website Maintainance
- WordPress website development
- Landing page design
- Website Security checkup
- Graphic design (banners, logos etc)

Web Designer
October 2021 - October 2021 (1 month)

Banaadir, Somalia

as a freelancer October 2018 - October 2021 (3 years 1 month)

Upwork Wordpress Developer 2022 - Present (2 years) Sindh, Pakistan

Website Designer
Website Developer
Landing Page Designer
Elementor Expert
Ecommerce Website Development
CMS *(Learn management system)
Design

Freelancer.com Wordpress Developer July 2020 - Present (4 years 3 months)

Education

Governor Sindh Initiative for GenAI, Web3, and Metaverse Cloud Applied Generative AI Engineer, Artificial Intelligence